Dataset Link: https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/eren2222/complete-indonesia-stock-exchange-idx-2000-2024

The date the set contains a complete record of every single stock that is listed on the IDX, starting from 2000 to 2024.
The data set includes complete records of every single day, from 2000 to 2024 with each day containing the opening, closing high, low adjusted close and volume of every single stock.

However, for some companies, the data may only start from a certain point, and that's because the company only was listed on IDX starting from that first point, not from the very beginning. 

Please download the data set and put it in the same folder as the python notebook, as the data set is too big to upload to Github.
Please also make sure that the file matches the following hash signatures to verify the integrity of the file:

CRC32: ACF8279C
CRC64: 10004A1FF8907358
MD5: C48825E562BE2E881B03559C5EC6DEF7
SHA1: EDB08F097A34656C21F7EE921AB5F466BC317FF9